Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/nguyen-hoang-nam-b82722228 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

User Experience (UX)
UX Research
User Personas

Languages

Japanese (Professional Working)

Certifications

JLPT N2

Google UX Design (7 Course)

Nguyen Hoang Nam

UI UX Designer

Da Nang City, Vietnam

Summary

Experienced in UXUI, with web/app design experience in many fields such as: Insurance, e-commerce, document management. Master User Experience Design, System design, understand the constraints of technology, and come up with better UX solutions based on the balance between user needs and business goals.

Experience

FPT Software
UI UX Designer
April 2022 - Present (3 years)
Da Nang City, Vietnam

HUGS Agency Graphic Designer May 2020 - December 2021 (1 year 8 months) Da Nang City, Vietnam

Education

FPT Polytechnic College of Danang study, Graphic Design · (July 2020 - November 2022)